Guide to the William Dwight Franklin and the Continental Vocalists Collection, 1853 - 1867
William Dwight Franklin and the Continental Vocalists Collection, 1853 - 1867
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Franklin, W. D. (William Dwight)
1000-134
4
6
The Continental Vocalists, led by William Dwight Franklin, was a touring Connecticut singing group popular in the mid-19th century.
William Dwight Franklin and the Continental Vocalists Collection contains published and unpublished books of music and lyrics. It also contains financial information about the Continental Vocalists' tours, and programs, a scrapbook, and two photographs.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Acquired prior to 1980.
Biographical and Historical Note
The Continental Vocalists was a successful and popular band of four members, all Americans and natives of Connecticut. It is strongly believed that all group members had musical training, played instruments and sang. They toured the country singing pure music and were well received every place without regard to population, politics or religious beliefs. One member of the group, J. Wesley Smith, began performing as a young boy with his family as part of the Smith Family in 1840. Mr. Smith organized a company which he styled the American Vocalists. Mr. Smith receives credit for having first advanced the project of a Continental Band, to represent, in costume, the Patriots of 1776, while performing National music.
W.D. Franklin was born November 25, 1825, in Brooklyn, Connecticut and studied music at the Boston Teachers Institute. He taught guitar, violin, violoncello, and voice for eight years before helping to found the Continental Vocalists quartet. Franklin married Mary Barrett on September 4, 1843. Mrs. Franklin opened a millinery in the 1870s at 54 Broad St., Middletown, CT.
The Continental Vocalists first trip commenced September 1, 1853 and collected $5,503 in receipts. Members of the Continental Vocalists for the first two trips included: C.W. Huntington, New London, Conn.; W.D. Franklin, Norwich, Conn.; W.R. Frisbie, Branford, Conn.; J.W. Smith, South Glastenbury, Conn.; and J.A. Sterry, Agt., Norwich, Conn. The second trip ended May 29, 1855, when at Jamestown, Frisbie was bleeding at the lungs and they started immediately for home where he died July 9, 1855. The group continued to tour with a replacement of Frisbee. The Financial Journal gives a detailed account of the band's daily events from 1853 through 1857.
Collection Overview
William Dwight Franklin and the Continental Vocalists Collection contains published and unpublished books of music and lyrics. It also contains financial information about the Continental Vocalists' tours, and programs, a scrapbook, and two photographs.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Middletown, Conn.--History.; Franklin, W. D. (William Dwight); Continental Vocalists.; Choruses, Secular (Men’s voices) with instrumental ensemble --Scores and parts.; Photographs.; Concert tours.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Financial and Tour Information
  - Continental Vocalists Financial Journal, W.D. Franklin, Norwich, Conn. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Account of money received in connection with Continental Vocalists, commencing Sept. 1953. Members of the Company C.W. Huntington, New London, Conn, W.D. Franklin, Norwich, Conn, W.R. Frisbie, Branford, Conn, J.W. Smith, South Glastenbury, Conn, J.A. Sterry, Agt., Norwich, Conn. The Continental Vocalists' first trip commenced September 1853. It included 173 performances and took in $5,503.00. This financial journal lists all debits and credits from 1853 through 1867 for the Continental Vocalists as well as W.D. Franklin's expenses.
    The second trip featured 177 shows and took in $6,841.00 with the same members of the company. It commenced Sept. 4, 1855. Second trip ending May 29th of '55. At Jamestown Frisbie taken bleeding at the lungs. Started immediately for home where he died July 9 of '55.
    Members of the Continental Vocalists for the first two trips included: C.W. Huntington, New London, Conn.; W.D. Franklin, Norwich, Conn.; W.R. Frisbie, Branford, Conn.; J.W. Smith, South Glastenbury, Conn.; and J.A. Sterry, Agt., Norwich, Conn.
    Third trip of the Continental Vocalists commenced at Rocky Hill, Conn. on August 24, 1855. Members of company included: C.W. Huntington, New London, Conn.; W.D. Franklin, Norwich, Conn.; T.M. Watson, Holyoke, Mass.; J.W. Smith, South Glastonbury, Conn.; and J.A. Sterry, Agt., Norwich, Conn.
    Fourth trip of Continental Vocalists commenced at North Glastonbury, Conn. in April of 1856. Members of company included: W.D. Franklin, T.M. Watson, W.B. Hall, J.W. Smith, and W.B. Thompson, Agt.
    Fifth trip of Continental Vocalists commenced at South Glastobury, Conn., August 24, 1856. Members of company included: W.D. Franklin, T.M. Watson, W.B. Hall, J.W. Smith, Master William Lewis, violinist and W.B. Thompson Agt.
    Sixth trip of Continental Vocalists commenced at North Glastonbury, Conn. It included company members W.D. Franklin, T.M. Watson, W.B. Hall, J.W. Smith, W. Lewis, and W.B. Thompson Agt.
    Seventh trip commenced at Elmira, N.Y. in 1857. Members included W.D. Franklin, W.B. Hall, J.W. Smith, B.M. Watson, Master Lewis, and W.M. Bates Agt.
    Eighth trip was a spring and summer tour that commenced May 3, 1858.
    Ninth trip commenced Sept. 9, 1858. This was followed by a short winter trip.
    Later trips included a western trip commencing at New Britain, Conn., on May 2, 1860, and a trip with Panorama that commenced in 1861. The Continental Vocalists continued to perform and bring in receipts through 1864.
    In March 1865, the Continental Vocalists reorganized and members included: W.D. Franklin - 1st Tenor; J.W. Smith - 2nd Tenor; H.M. Rogers - Alto; and A.W. Woodward - Bass.
    Additional entries for debits and credits are included for trips through 1867.
  - W.D. Franklin Journal (Folder 2)
    This book is a combination of journal and scrapbook. It includes original writings as well as entry passes, tickets, articles, songs, programs, drawings and announcements regarding Continental Vocalists or their members. It is unfortunate that this scrapbook's pasted-in material has been glued over original writings. An advertisement lists Mr. W.D. Franklin as instructor of Musical Instruction and Cultivation of the Voice.
  - Scraps (Folder 3)
    Inside cover reads Done at Madison, Wisconsin, Nov. 21st /58 'Continental Vocalists' Scrap Book Company Members: W.D. Franklin, J.W. Smith, T.M. Watson, W.A. Lewis, W.M. Bates Agt. This scrapbook contains articles, letters, advertisements, concert passes, tickets, and announcements. The items in this scrapbook are from 1857 and 1858 and includes publications from places they performed during that time such as the Hartford Courant.
  - Mr. and Mrs. W.D. Franklin Announcements and Publicity (Folder 4)
    Contents include:
    Photograph of Continental Vocalists with Watson, Lewis, Franklin, and Smith.
    Negative and photograph of Smith, Franklin, Rogers, and Watson.
    W.D. Franklin business card.
    Continental Vocalists Programme.
    Gospel and educational temperance contribution card.
    Our Thematic Catalogue of the Latest Music Vocal and Instrumental, Denton, Cottier and Daniels, Buffalo, N.Y.
    1873: The Stage Mirror, Lancaster, PA newspaper
    1874 invitation: Fall and Winter Opening, Mrs. W.D. Franklin Millinery
    1876 programme: Centennial Concert at Ye Methodist Meeting House
    1877 announcement card: Mrs. W.D. Franklin's Millinery Opening on 54 Broad St., Middletown
    1878 programme: Eleventh Convention of the Connecticut Sunday School Teachers' Association in the South Congregational Church, Middletown, Conn.
    1881 advertisement: New England Prohibition Pic-Nic
    March 1892: note regarding Mr. and Mrs. Franklin from H.E. Parker, Pastor M.E. Church
- Music Books and Notebooks
  This series contains a collection of books with lyrics and music of songs performed by the Continental Vocalists. Most of the music books in this box appear to have belonged to William Dwight Franklin. The Old Folks Music Book and the Glee Book are printed; the other lyrics and music are handwritten into music notebooks.
  - Old Folks Music Book (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Includes an unbound 1860 edition and a bound 1874 edition. The unbound version belonged to W.D. Franklin.
    Title page reads, Father Kemp's Old Folks Concert Music. A Collection of the Most Favorite Tunes of Billings, Swan, Holden, Read, Kimball, Ingalls and Others. To which is added a variety of Anthems and Choruses, and Divers Patriotic and Other Songs of the Greatest and Best Composers.
    Entered according to Act of Congress, in the year 1874, by O. Ditson & Co., in the Office of the Librarian of Congress at Washington.
    - All Hail the Power of Jesus' Name, Holden
    - America (My Country 'Tis of Thee)
    - Anthem for Easter, Billings
    - Anvil Chorus, Verdi
    - Auld Lang Syne (Song of the Old Folks)
    - The Battle of Stonington
    - Before Jehovah's Awful Throne, M. Madan
    - Blessing, S. Stanley
    - Blue Hill, Belknap
    - Boston, Billings
    - Bridgewater, Edson
    - Buckfield, Maxim
    - Cambridge, Dr. Randall
    - Celestial Watering, Ingalls
    - Chester, Billings
    - "Child of Mortality, Bray
    - China, T. Swan
    - Complaint, Parmeter
    - Confidence, Holden
    - Cousin Jedediah, H.S. Thompson
    - David's Lamentation, Billings
    - The Dearest Spot of Earth to Me is Home, W.A. Wrighton
    - Devotion, Read
    - The Dying Christian, Harwood
    - German Hymn, Pleyel
    - Greenwich, Read
    - Hail Columbia
    - Home Again
    - Invitation, Kimball
    - Jerusalem, My Glorious Home, Dr. Lowell Mason, 1840
    - John Brown, or Glory, Glory, Hallelujah!
    - Kidd's Lament
    - Lenox, Edson
    - Lisbon, Read
    - Majesty, Billings
    - Marseilles Hymn
    - Montgomery, Morgan
    - Mear, Williams' Coll.
    - Milford, Stephenson
    - Montague, Swan
    - Mount Sion
    - My Grandma's Advice
    - Nearer, My God to Thee, Dr. Mason
    - New Durham, Austin
    - New Jerusalem, Ingalls
    - Northfield, Ingalls
    - Ocean, Swan
    - Ode to Science, Swan
    - Old Folks at Home, Foster
    - Old Hundred, Martin Luther
    - Plainfield, Kimball
    - Portland, Maxim
    - Rainbow
    - Revolutionary Tea
    - Russia, Read
    - St. Martin's, Tansur
    - St. Thomas, Williams' Coll.
    - Sherburne, Read
    - Silver Street, I. Smith
    - Song of the Old Folks (Auld Lang Syne)
    - Sons of Zion Come Before Him, Nauman
    - Sound the Loud Timbrel, Avison
    - The Star Spangled Banner
    - Strike the Cymbal, Pucita
    - Turner, Maxim
    - Victory, Read
    - When George the Third was King
    - Windsor, Kirby
    - Within a Mile of Edinboro' Town
    - Worcester, Wood
    - Yankee Doodle (Yankee Return from Camp)
    - Yankee Return from Camp (Yankee Doodle)
  - Glee Book (Folder 2)
    This hardcover book contains the lyrics and music to the Continental Vocalists songs. Members include Charles W. Huntington of New London, CT, William D. Franklin of Norwich, CT, William R. Frisbie of Branford, CT and J. Wesley Smith of South Glastenbury, CT.
    Title page: The Continental Vocalists' Glee Book, Comprising the Songs, Quartetts, Etc. of the Famous Continental Vocalists, and Rendered so Popular by them Throughout the Country by their Unique and Inimitable Performances. Also a biography of each member of the Troupe, written by their business conductor, John A. Sterry, Esq. The whole arranged, harmonized and partly composed by themselves.
    Entered according to Act of Congress, in the year 1855, by J.E. Gould, in the Clerk's Office of the District Court in and for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania.
    Inside cover includes a handwritten Magnolia Song and a note: Please Return to W.D. Franklin, South Glastenbury, Conn.
    - Ah! For Wings; or Primma Donna Song
    - By the Sad Sea Waves
    - Call Me Pet Names
    - Come let us Ramble
    - Continentals' Farewell Glee
    - Do they miss me at Home?
    - E Pluribus Unum
    - Good Night
    - In this Old Chair
    - It is better to Laugh
    - Jamie's on the Stormy Sea
    - Joe Hardy
    - Johnny Sands
    - Katy Darling
    - Light Sparks
    - Lilly Dale
    - Lulu is our Darling Pride
    - Not for Gold or Precious Stones
    - Our Welcome Glee
    - Rail Toad Chorus
    - Recollections of Home
    - Serenade of Don Pasquale
    - She Sweetly Sleeps
    - Silence! Silence!
    - Song of the Olden Time
    - The Flag of Our Union
    - The Highland Brothers
    - The Land of the West
    - The Mariner Loves o'er the Waters to Roam
    - The Merry Sleigh Ride
    - The Mountain Bugle
    - The Origin of Yankee Doodle
    - The Raven
    - The Tempest
    - The Wild Old Woods
    - There's a Sigh in the Heart
    - Three Bells
    - 'Tis the Last Rose of Summer
    - War Song of the Texan Rangers
    - We Meet by Chance
    - We Miss Thee at Home
  - Music Notebook (Folder 3)
    Cover missing. The writing in this notebook may not belong to W.D. Franklin.
    - What Shall it Be? Rev. J.T. Wright
    - The Syrian Shephard Song
    - The Muzzin's (sp?) Call to Prayers
  - Continental Vocalists, February 1865 (Folder 4)
    Notebook of words and music.
    - Hail Glorious Banner
    - A Very Young Man, Frank
    - Typed insert with words to four songs; E Pluribus Unum, The Sword of Bunker Hill, Star Spangled Banner, and A Thousand a Year.
    - Haste On the Battle
    - Tis Sweet to be Remembered
    - Touch the Gate Gently
    - Yanks Doodle (?)
    - List These Sounds So Softly Stealing
    - The Wanderer Boys Song
    - Misteries of Rehearsals Recite The Raven
    - Moonlight and Starlight
    - Cousin Jedidiah
    - General Scott and Corporal Johnson
    - Fling Out the Old Banner
    - The Tempest
    - O! Give Me Music
    - Echo Song or Ego and Echo, Poetry by Saxe, Music and Chorus by W.D. Franklin
    - Hail to Our Beautiful Land
    - The Beautiful Shore of Time, Music and Poetry by W.D. Franklin - Harmonized by Rogers
    - Let Us Joy and be Happy to Night, Opening Glee, Music and Poetry by W.D. Franklin
    - Come This Day, Harmonized by W.D. Franklin
    - When the Joys of Youth are O'er, by W.D. Franklin
    - Let Us Love Each Other Fondly
    - The Snow Storm
  - Music Notebook (Folder 5)
    Inside back cover reads: W.P. Robinson, Local Ed. Of Daily Adv. Auburn, N.Y.
    First page seems to be missing.
    - I Love the Night
    - Yankee Doodle
    - O Give Me Music
    - The Raven a chant
    - Rail Road Chorus
    - My School Boy Days
    - The Union
    - Operatic Smith
    - Farewell Glee
    - Bright Be Our Parting
    - W'er Happy to Night
    - The Fay of the Falls
    - Hark I Hear the Angels Sing
    - The Battle Prayer by Himmel
    - Marseilles Hymn
    - A Few Inquiries
    - The Union
    - Mount Vernon Bells
    - Soldiers Love
    - The Snow Storm
    - The Old Clock
    - The Gamblers Wife
    - Soldiers Love
    - Hie the Shallop
    - The Old Bachelor and Happy Husbands
    - Hunting Glee
    - The Song of the Night
    - Ault Lang Syne
    - Beautiful Silver Sea
    - Napolitain
    - Hurrah for the Land of the Free W.D. Franklin
    - Viva'l America Home of the Free
    - Is It Anybody's Business
    - Free for Three Girls
    - To the Memory of our Singing Canary 'Dick'
    - List, the Evening Breeze is Stealing
    - Hunting Song
    - Interlude by a Glover
    - Stars of the Summer Night
    - One Pair of Stocking to Mend to Night
  - W.D. Franklin, South Glastonbury, Conn., Continental Vocalists (Folder 6)
    Music notebook contains lyrics, music or brief instrumental arrangements on songs.
    - Our Welcome Glee
    - Eighty Years Ago
    - The Beautiful Silver Sea
    - The Monks of Old
    - A Curious Song
    - The Rocky Mountain Boys
    - The American Eagle
    - The Echoing Horn
    - The Sons of Harmonie
    - Gaffer Green and Robin Ruff
    - Our Starry Flag
    - The Home of My Boyhood
    - Annie Laurie
    - Stars of the Summer Night
    - The Grave of Washington
    - Hurra Hurra for the Union
    - The Flag of Our Union
  - W.D. Franklin, Small music notebook (Folder 7)
    - When the Joys of Youth are O'er
    - Rock of Ages
    - Softly the (?)
    - There is Light Beyond the River
    - The Mellow Notes of the Hunter's Horn
    - Blest are the Dead
    - The Monks of Old
  - W.D. Franklin, Small music notebook (Folder 8)
    - Widow Bedott's Chant
    - Tobacco Song composed at Reading, Ohio by Frank
    - Columbia Remember the Heroes harmony at Norwich by Continentals
    - The Sword of Bunker Hill
    - The Continental's Farewell Glee
    - The Last Review
    - Typed copy of Searching for the Sea
  - W.D. Franklin, South Glastonbury, Conn., Music Notebook (Folder 9)
    - Old Ironsides
    - When This Cruel War is Over
    - Blue Beard
    - The Monks of Old
    - Twelve O'Clock
    - Typed copy of Lulu is Our Darling Pride
    - Typed copy of Softly Now the Light of Day
    - Typed copy of The Old Couple
  - W.D. Franklin, Continental Vocalists South Glastonbury, Conn. (Folder 10)
    Notebook of handwritten lyrics and music.
    - Skin-plaster Song
    - Our Welcome Glee, by L. Marshall
    - The Battle Prayer, by Kimmel (sp?)
    - Eighty Years Ago, by Butcher
    - I Care for Them Tenderly, Poetry by Rev. Bumerton, Music by Frank
    - Hark! To the Distant Bugle, by Perkins
    - Arm Brothers Arm, Poetry by Bourne, Music by Frank
    - The Rocky Mountain Boys
    - The Flag of Our Union, Bardbury
    - A Curious Song, Poetry by Frank, Music Continentals
    - The Brave Volunteer, by Frank
    - Hail Glorious Banner, Poetry Mrs. Mary Moore, Music C. Warren
    - Natalie
    - The Maid of the Mill, Peters
    - I See Her Still in my Dreams, Foster
    - Beautiful Silver Sea, by Clark
    - Columbia the Gem of the Ocean, by Shaw
    - Hark I Hear An Angel Sing, Shivall
    - The Mellow Notes of the Hunters Horn
    - Come in the Quiet Evening, Music and Poetry by Franklin
    - Dixie, Parody by Frank
    - Care for them Tenderly, Music by Stevens
    - The Virginia Rose Bud, by Kavanaugh
    - My Own One
    - The Rataplan
    - Towanda March, June 7, 1862
    - Hurrah For the Land of the Free, Franklin
    - The Clarion Now Sounds to the Fields, Maeder
    - Simon the Cellarer, by Hatton
    - The Union Oath
    - John Brown Camp Song, Poetry Frank
    - They Wer Sitting Side by Side
    - March Away Cherrily, Music by George H. Russell
    - Mountain Bugle Song, W.D. Franklin
  - W.D. Franklin, Music Notebook (Folder 11)
    First page reads: Collection of Songs Sung By W.D. Franklin of Middletown, Conn. 1878 & 9.
    This notebook contains the lyrics to songs sung by W.D. Franklin but not the music.
    - My Redeemer
    - Trust in the Lord
    - Tell Me More About Jesus
    - Jesus is Waiting at the Gate
    - Hallelujah What a Savior
    - 'Tis Sweet to be Remembered
    - Are Your Windows Open Toward Jerusalem?
    - There is Light Beyond the River
    - Wonderful Words of Life
    - The Mistakes of My Life
    - Savior by Clinging to the (?)
    - Trusting Jesus
    - The Ninety and Nine
    - There's a Beautiful World
    - Youth Manhood and Age
    - There is a Green Hill far Away
    - Mey Ain Countrie
    - I Love to Tell the Story
    - Safe Within the Veil
    - Hallelujah 'Tis Done
    - Jesus Said It All
    - It May Be Too Late
    - Mary of Argyle
    - All In the Mist of the Morning
    - Nazareth
    - Friends of Long Ago
    - Franklin's Good Night
    - King Bacchus
    - Christ is Coming Back Again January 12th, 1897
  - Manuscript Music of 'W.D. Franklin' Book No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    This book contains handwritten lyrics and music to a collection of W.D. Franklin songs. First page reads: Franklin's Group of Songs. Containing Five Successful Concert Numbers. First Number - 'The Voyage of Life' song, Second Number - 'The Mountain Bugle Echo Song' ballad, Third Number - 'The Old Corporal of Descriptive Patriotic' ballad, Fourth Number - 'Twilight Dreaming' quartette or song, Fifth Number - 'Good Night' a beautiful closing song. By W.D. Franklin - Organizer of the Old Continental Vocalists (Huntington, Frisbie, Franklin, Smith)
    - Let Us Joy and Be Happy To Night
    - My School Boy Days, published music
    - Let Us Love Each Other Fondly', ballad poetry and music
    - That Crutch In the Corner Yonder, poetry by John McIntosh
    - Beautiful Starlight 'Echo Song'
    - The American Flag
    - The Echoes of Song, solo and chorus
    - Pipers Favorite
    - Let Us Have Peace
    - The Dead Colonel in the Blue
    - Knickerbocker Set
    - Mountain Bugle Song, quartette, music and poetry by W.D. Franklin of Continental Vocalists as sung by them at their concerts
    - Come in Beautiful Dreams
    - Good Night Beloved
    - What Folks Say, poetry selected, humorous solo and chorus
    - The Cottage by the Glen, ballad published music, written at Louisville, KY 1846
    - Come This Way, quartette, harmonies from "Pixley" done at Norwich, Conn., 1854
    - Linger Not Long, ballad, music, writtenat So. Glastenbury, Conn., July 1865
    - The Widow Bedetts Chant, harmony, South Glastenbury, Conn.
    - The Rude Boy, humorous chant, from Noah Webster
    - Tis Sweet to Be Remembered, Composed by H.M. Rogers, ballad
    - Yankee Doodle, poetry, The Continentals
    - A Seale of Six Days in Wall St., a humorous chant, music
    - The Beautiful Shore of Time, quartette, poetry and music
    - The Miller of the Sea, song, music
    - The Farmers Song, W.D. Franklin
    - The Miller of the Dee, W.D. Franklin
    - Star of the Evening, by A.A. Starry
    - Memory Bells, poetry by P. Vining
    - Cradle Song, W.D. Franklin
    - A Dollar or Two, W.D. Franklin
    - Our Dear Nature Home, music by J.B. Bearslie
  - Music Book, numbered songs (Folder 2)
    - No. 1, Knickerbocker Set
    - No. (?), Fill De Regiment Set
    - No. 7, Polka Set
    - No. 8, Medly Set
    - No. 9, Christy's 1st Set, clarinet
    - No. 10, Christy's 2nd Set
    - No. 11, Master Humphrey's Set
    - No. 12, Dartmouth Set
    - No. 13. Forest Quadrille 1st Set
    - No. 14, Forset Quadrille 2nd Set
    - No. 15, Concert Hall Set
    - No. 16, Bethoven Set
    - No. 17, (?) Adelaide's Set
    - No. 18, March in Norma
    - No. 19, Cheat and Prisnor Set
    - Pipers Favorit
  - School Music, W. D. Franklin, 54 Broad St. (Folder 3)
    Middletown School Festival Music, 7 copies
    - No. 1, To God on High
    - No. 2, The Praise of God
    - No. 3, Village Bells
    - No. 4, Evening Song
    - No. 5, So Merrily Over the Ocean Spray
    - No. 6, Freedom's Day
    - No. 7, Evening Song
    - No. 8, Far Away the Camp-fires Burn
    - No. 9, The Heaving Billow
    - No. 10, The Old Hundreth Psalm
  - Guitar Music (Folder 4)
    - A Collection of Favorite Songs of the Day Arranged for the Guitar by Sep. Winner: She Sang Among the Flowers
    - Musical Bazaar: A Collection of Songs and Ballads Arranged for the Guitar: The Old Playground
    - Gems of the Season. Arranged for the Guitar by W.L. Hayden: Prayer for Moses in Egypt
    - Peter's Collection of Standard Guitar Songs: Take Me Back Home
    - Peter's Collection of Standard Guitar Songs: Lorena
    - Peter's Collection of Standard Guitar Songs: Laura Lee
  - Violin and Piano (Folder 5)
    - Violin and Piano, Blumenlese, (Harvest Flowers.) by Jul. Weiss
      Harvest of Flowers 'Blumenlese' Containing a Choice Collection of Popular Melodies, Together With Selections from the Operas. Arranged in: An Easy and Instructive Manner by Jul. Weiss
  - Music Publications (Folder 6)